Hello, friend, welcome back.
In this video, I'll discuss about iOS, every JavaScript program, I should know about this iOS six.
In this course, I will use this keyword lots of time.
So better to know.
Little idea about this later.
I will also convert one total another section for these iOS six.
What is iOS six full meaning of iOS six?
Is it my script?
Six Here it means an organization which is responsible for defining a standard in general concept.
iOS six is modern update of JavaScript, widely known as Chair six.
Here six is the JavaScript version name.
So what is the latest version of JavaScript in now?
When I'm recording this course is 2015 is the latest version of JavaScript programming languages.
It is the first major update to JavaScript since 1997.
It was approved in June 2015 by EMI International.
As I told you, that is one of the association responsible for approving EMI standards switch programming
languages like JavaScript, Coffee Scripts and TypeScript.
The name of this version of JavaScript has undergone multiple changes, starting from Harmony to iOS
six two years 2015 before EA's 2015 EMI script was named after the version number.
It was only recently that it was decided that it will be name according of the year of release.
For that reason, the name change is seeks two years 2015.
I hope you get some idea about iOS six.
Later will go more deep suffering in our next video, and instead another session is will be JavaScript
variable and other types.
Everything I will cover one by one.
I hope you like it.
Very much so.
Thanks for watching.
I will see you in the next video.